<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Nicolas Carolo</title>
    <link>https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Nicolas Carolo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nicolas Carolo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 15:27:25 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Auru</title>
      <link>https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/auru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 15:27:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/auru/</guid>
      <description>.--. .-. .-.,---. .-. .-. / /\ \ | | | || .-.\ | | | | / /__\ \| | | || `-&#39;/ | | | | | __ || | | || ( | | | | | | |)|| `-&#39;)|| |\ \ | `-&#39;)| |_| (_)`---(_)|_| \)\`---(_) (__) A shell script for keeping AUR packages up-to-date Author: Nicolas Carolo nicolascarolo.dev@gmail.com
Copyright: © 2020, Nicolas Carolo.
Date: 2020-04-04</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hsploit</title>
      <link>https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/hsploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:17:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/hsploit/</guid>
      <description>hsploit is an advanced command-line search engine for Exploit-DB
Author: Nicolas Carolo nicolascarolo.dev@gmail.com
Copyright: © 2019, Nicolas Carolo.
Date: 2019-12-03
Version: 1.7.1
PURPOSE hsploit is an advanced command-line search engine for Exploit-DB developed in Python, born with the aim of showing the user the most accurate search results.
Features  Effective version number filtering Open the source code of exploits and shellcodes using nano View information about the characteristics of exploits and shellcodes Automatic check for updates  Effective version number filtering examples Example I nicolas@carolo:~$ searchsploit WordPress 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HoundSploit</title>
      <link>https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/houndsploit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 23:28:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nicolas-carolo.github.io/projects/houndsploit/</guid>
      <description>HoundSploit is an advanced search engine for Exploit-DB developed in Python using Django Web Framework, born with the aim of showing the user the most accurate search results.
Features  Effective version number filtering Advanced filtering Search suggestions with customization Syntax highlighting of the source code of exploits and shellcodes Downloading of the source code of exploits and shellcodes Highlighting of searched words in search results Automatic check for updates  Effective version number filtering examples Example I nicolas@carolo:~$ searchsploit WordPress 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>